Guide to the Peter Paul Kellogg papers, 1934-1964
Kellogg, Peter Paul papers, 1934-1964
- "Voices of the Night" (Cornell), 4 records (Box 13, Folder 8)
- Carl Weismann - "De Syngende Hunde" -, slightly clipped 1 record (Box 13, Folder 9)
- "Songs of Insects" (Cornell) -, slightly chipped 1 record (Box 13, Folder 10)
- "Songs of Wild Birds," Nicholson and Koch, 2 records & 1 handbook (Box 13, Folder 11)
- Carl Weisman - "Sounds of Danish Nature", 10 records (Box 14, Folder 1)
- "Western Bird Songs of Dooryard, Field, and Forest", 1 record (Box 14, Folder 2)
- "Songs of Our Native Birds" (Charles Kellogg), 1 record (Box 14, Folder 3)
- "American Bird Songs" (Cornell), volume II, 25 records (Box 14, Folder 4)
- "American Bird Songs" (Cornell), "Birds of Northern Gardens and Shade Trees (smaller red record), 1 record (Box 14)
- Early Cornell records privately produced and distributed, 6 records (Box 14, Folder 5)
- "Bird Songs Recorded from Nature" (First record ever published by Cornell Laboratory and Scully), 1 record (Box 14, Folder 6)
- "Gesiederte Meistersänger": The first sound patterns and manual for observation and determination of nature birds, Oskar Heinroth, 1 handbook and 3 records (Box 15, Folder 1)
- Bird Songs in Your Garden - Arthur A. Allen, text and photographs; P.P. Kellogg, recordings (Cornell), 1961 (Box 15, Folder 2)
- Evening in Sapsucker Woods, Allan and Kellogg (Cornell), 1 record (Box 15, Folder 3)
- Field Guide to Western Bird Songs, Kellogg, Allen and R.T. Peterson, 3 records (Box 15, Folder 4)
- "Birds on a May Morning", 1 record (Box 16, Folder 1)
- "The Songs of Insects" (Cornell), 1 record (Box 16, Folder 2)
- "Voices of the Sea", 1 record (Box 16, Folder 3)
- "Voices of the Night" (Cornell), 1 record (Box 16, Folder 4)
- "Sounds of North American Frogs", 1 record and 1 manual (Box 16, Folder 5)
- "Sound Patterns", 1 record (Box 16, Folder 6)
- "Voices of African Birds" (Cornell), 1 record (Box 16, Folder 7)
- "Songs of East African Birds" (Queenie), 3 records (Box 16, Folder 8a)
- "Bird Songs of Lake Nyibor" (Queenie), 1 record (Box 16, Folder 8b)
- "Sounds of Midway", 1 record (Box 16, Folder 9)
- "Listen to the Mocking Bird" (Charles Kellogg), 1 record (Box 16, Folder 10)
- "East African Bird Songs", 1 record (Box 16, Folder 11)
- "Sound Reproductions of a Tropical Forest", 1 record (Box 16, Folder 12)
- "Underwater Calls of the White Whale", 1 record (Box 16, Folder 13)
- The A. A. Allen Retirement Party at Lehigh Valley House, 1950, 5 records (Box 16, Folder 14)
- Talking Books (Cornell) (Box 17)
  - American Bird Biographies - Allen
  - American Bird Songs - Allen
  - Wild Birds and Their Songs - Brand, 31 records
- "Recordings Made at Bronx Zoo," 1944 (Cornell), 7 records (Box 18, Folder 1)
- "Jungle Sounds" (Cornell), 1 record (Box 18, Folder 2)
- "Recordings of Jungle Sounds" (Cornell), 2 records, 1 manual (Box 18, Folder 3)
- Jungle Recordings Pressings (Cornell), 18 records (Box 18, Folder 4)
- "Voices of the Night" Pressings (Cornell), 4 records (Box 18, Folder 5)